Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 70, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: On the Welfare, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Author: Georgina M. Smith
    Notes: May 1967
  - Item 9: Iowa's Human and Community Development Resources, Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Author: Iowa Manpower Development Council
  - Item 10: Social Welfare Project, 1955; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Box: 70, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Administration of the Wage Stop, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Social Security
  - Item 2: Social Services in Britain, Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
    Author: Great Britain Central Office of Information
  - Item 3: The Cost of Social Services, Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
    Author: John Vaizey
  - Item 4: The Social Services: Needs and Means, Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
    Author: J. Enoch Powell
- Box: 70, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Community Development Programmes in Greece, 1953; Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Box: 70, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Expanding Frontiers in Social Welfare, 1960; Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    Author: Doroty Lally
    Notes: August 1960
- Box: 70, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Public Welfare, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    Author: New York Board of Social Welfare
  - Item 2: Improvement of Public Welfare Administration, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    Notes: June 1966
  - Item 3: Social Welfare Services in New York State, 1948; Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    Notes: August 1948
  - Item 4: Public Social Services in New York State, 1950; Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    Notes: November 1, 1950
- Box: 70, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Public Welfare Personnel, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    Notes: May 1968
- Box: 70, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Social Welfare in the U.K. Dependencies, Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
- Box: 70, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: A Survey of the Current Relief Situation in Twenty-Eight Selected Areas of the United States, 1937; Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
    Author: American Association of Social Workers
    Notes: February 15, 1937
  - Item 2: Social Welfare Administration in the United States of America, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
    Author: U.S. Social Security Administration
  - Item 3: A Constructive Public Welfare Program, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Economics and Public Welfare, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Welfare Reform, 1969; Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Ways and Means
  - Item 6: Having the Power, We Have the Duty, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
    Author: Advisory Council on Public Welfare
  - Item 7: Problems in Attaining Integrity in Welfare Programs, 1972; Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
    Notes: March 16, 1972
  - Item 8: A Report from The Steering Committee, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
    Author: The Steering Committee
  - Item 9: Public Welfare, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
    Author: Emma Harrison
  - Item 10: Disability, Incapacity, and Rehabilitation Referral, 1972; Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
    Notes: January 1972
  - Item 11: Welfare Provisions, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: Social Welfare in a Changing World, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: Administrative Approaches to Staff Development in Public Welfare Agencies, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 14: Welfare Provisions, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: Statistical Information Related to Family Assistance Provisions, 1971; Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
    Notes: February 24, 1971
- Box: 70, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Welfare Programs for Families, 1971; Publication (Box 70, Folder 16)
    Author: Russell B. Long
    Notes: July 21, 1971
  - Item 2: Major Federal Legislation Affecting Social Welfare, Publication (Box 70, Folder 16)
    Author: U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Finance
  - Item 3: Welfare Reform -- Or is it?, 1971; Publication (Box 70, Folder 16)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Finance
    Notes: August 6, 1971
- Box: 70, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Financing Public Welfare, Publication (Box 70, Folder 17)
    Author: The Council of State Governments
- Box: 70, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: P.W.A. and Industry, Publication (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Box: 70, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: the Executive's Publicity Manual, Publication (Box 70, Folder 19)
    Author: Denny Griswold
- Box: 70, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Que Pasa in Puerto Rico, 1959; Publication (Box 70, Folder 20)
    Author: Governors' Conference
    Notes: August 1959
  - Item 2: Strangers then Neighbors, Publication (Box 70, Folder 20)
    Author: Clarence Senior
- Box: 70, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: the Puerto-Rican Workers in New York, Publication (Box 70, Folder 21)
    Author: Lois Gray
- Box: 70, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Puerto Rican in New Jersey, 1955; Publication (Box 70, Folder 22)
    Author: Isham B. Jones
    Notes: July 1955
- Box: 70, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Puerto Rican Population of the New York City Area, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 23)
    Author: New York Commission for Human Rights
    Notes: May 1962
  - Item 2: Occupations of Puerto Ricans in New York City, Publication (Box 70, Folder 23)
    Author: New York Department of Labor
  - Item 3: Puerto Rican Workers in New York City, 1954; Publication (Box 70, Folder 23)
    Author: Columbia University
    Notes: January 1954
  - Item 4: Puerto Rican Integration in the Skirt Industry in New York City, 1959; Publication (Box 70, Folder 23)
    Author: New York Commission Against Discrimination
- Box: 70, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Health and Welfare Needs in New York State, 1960; Publication (Box 70, Folder 24)
    Author: State Charities Aid Association
    Notes: January 1960
- Box: 70, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Balance of Social, Economic, and Demographic Change in Puerto Rico, Publication (Box 70, Folder 25)
    Author: Cornell University
  - Item 2: Dependence of the Puerto Rican Economy on the Development on its Human Resources, 1970; Publication (Box 70, Folder 25)
    Author: Puerto Rico Development Group
  - Item 3: Official Record of Area Redevelopment Administration Conference, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 25)
    Author: University of Puerto Rico
    Notes: March 1-3, 1962
- Box: 70, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Puerto Rican Farm Workers, Publication (Box 70, Folder 26)
    Author: Pennsylvania Bureau of Employment Security
- Box: 70, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Industry in Puerto Rico, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 27)
    Author: Chase Manhattan Bank
    Notes: July 1967
- Box: 70, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Why do Employees Resign?, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 28)
    Notes: April 1966
  - Item 2: Why They Quit, Publication (Box 70, Folder 28)
    Author: Robert D. Loken
  - Item 3: Determinants of the Differences in Quit Rate Among Industries, Publication (Box 70, Folder 28)
- Box: 70, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Race: What the World's Scientists Say, Publication (Box 70, Folder 29)
    Author: South African Institute of Race Relations
- Box: 70, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Racial Discrimination, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 30)
    Author: Ulf Himmelstrand
- Box: 70, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 70, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Black Masses as Vanguard, 1970; Publication (Box 70, Folder 31)
    Author: National Editorial Board of News & Letters
    Notes: August 1970
- Box: 70, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 70, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Sport and Race in South Africa, Publication (Box 70, Folder 32)
    Author: Mary Draper
  - Item 2: Action Reaction and Counteraction, Publication (Box 70, Folder 32)
    Author: Muriel Horrell
  - Item 3: Separate Development: the Challenge of the Transkei, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 32)
    Author: Gwendolen M. Carter
- Box: 70, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 70, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Political Systems in Multi-Racial Societies, Publication (Box 70, Folder 33)
    Author: Kenneth A. Heard
  - Item 2: The Races of Mankind, Publication (Box 70, Folder 33)
    Author: Ruth Benedict & Gene Weltfish
- Box: 70, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 70, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: The Police and Race Relations, Publication (Box 70, Folder 34)
    Author: American Jewish Committee
- Box: 70, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 70, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Intergroup Relations, Publication (Box 70, Folder 35)
    Author: New York University
- Box: 70, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 70, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Prohibiting Certain Coercive Practices Affecting Radio Broadcasting, 1946; Publication (Box 70, Folder 36)
    Author: U.S. House of Representatives
    Notes: January 29, 1946
  - Item 2: Interference with Broadcasting of Noncommercial Educational Programs, 1945; Publication (Box 70, Folder 36)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce
- Box: 70, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 70, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Brief Summary of State Laws and Regulations for the Control of Radiation Hazards, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 37)
- Box: 70, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 70, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Dammen Distrikt Konduktorforening, Publication (Box 70, Folder 38)
    Author: Per O. Lian, Normann Solberg, Rolf Dramdahl
    Language: Norwegian.
- Box: 71, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: How to Sell Railroad Traffic, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Author: E.G. Plowman
- Box: 71, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Provisions of the Railroad Retirement Act and the Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Author: Railroad Retirement Board
    Notes: May 1966
  - Item 2: Public Law 572, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Box: 71, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Railroad Retirement Act, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
    Notes: September 27, 1966
  - Item 2: Railroad Retirement Benefits, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Box: 71, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Memorandum, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Author: Jesse Clark
  - Item 2: Trains and the Men Who Run Them, 1954; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Author: Alexander Uhl
  - Item 3: Newsletter, 1960; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Author: Rail Operating Brotherhoods
    Notes: November 1960
  - Item 4: Fast New Trains Could Unclog Megalopolis, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Author: Richard A. Rice
    Notes: Fall 1966
  - Item 5: Railroads, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Author: Association of American Railroads
    Notes: December 25, 1966
  - Item 6: List of Principal Railroads in the United States, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: U.S. Survival and the Railroads, 1961; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Author: U.S. Congress
    Notes: December 4, 1961
  - Item 8: Railroad Review and Outlook, 1969; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: PRR + NYC Spells Economic Ruin for Pennsylvania, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Author: Milton J. Sharp
  - Item 10: Operating Statistics of Large Railroads, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Author: Interstate Commerce Commission
  - Item 11: Railroad Merger Scoreboard, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Notes: November 1966
  - Item 12: Statistics of Railroads of Class I, 1974; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Notes: August 1974
  - Item 13: Research and Tomorrow's Railroads, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Author: W.M. Keller
    Notes: August 9-16, 1965
  - Item 14: Impact of Transportation Policy on Railroad Labor, 1960; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Author: G.E. Leighty
    Notes: September 21, 1960
  - Item 15: The American Railway Industry, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Author: Carlton J. Corliss
  - Item 16: Who Gets the Railroad Dollar?, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Box: 71, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Accident-Prone Employee, Publication (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Author: The Cleveland Railway Company
- Box: 71, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Symposium on Cybernetics, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Author: Union International des Chemins de Fer
    Notes: November 4- 13, 1963
  - Item 2: Automation in the Railroad Industry, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Author: W.P. Kennedy
  - Item 3: New Views on Automation, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Box: 71, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Bibliography of Railroad Literature, Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: A List of Books for Possible Use in Teaching or Studying Railroad Transportation in Colleges or Universities, 1961; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
    Notes: October 1961
  - Item 3: Railroads Consolidation, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
    Author: Bureau of Railway Economics Library
  - Item 4: Railroads Abandonment, 1964; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Box: 71, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Story of the Boxcars, 1948; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Notes: April 1, 1948
- Box: 71, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: El Nivel de Vida de los Trabajadores Ferroviarios, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 9)
    Author: Universidad Nacional de Colombia
    Language: Spanish.
- Box: 71, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Railroad Merger Scoreboard, 1967; Publication (Box 71, Folder 10)
    Notes: March 1967
- Box: 71, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Labor Situation, 1920; Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
    Author: W.W. Atterbury
    Notes: November 18, 1920
  - Item 2: Railroads v. Employees, Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
    Author: Franklin County Court
  - Item 3: Worker Protection in Railroad Mergers, 1963; Publication (Box 71, Folder 11)
    Author: University of Georgia
    Notes: December 1963
- Box: 71, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Railroad Mileage Pay, 1961; Publication (Box 71, Folder 12)
    Author: Jules Backman
    Notes: February 1961
- Box: 71, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Brief, 1938; Publication (Box 71, Folder 13)
    Author: Hayward Brief Co.
    Notes: March 31, 1938
- Box: 71, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Trailer-on-Flatcar Service, 1960; Publication (Box 71, Folder 14)
    Author: American Association of Railroads
- Box: 71, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Der GdED Ratgeber, Publication (Box 71, Folder 15)
    Author: Verlag der GdED
- Box: 71, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Report, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 16)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Labour
    Notes: September 1965
- Box: 71, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Railroad Land Grant Legend in American History Texts, 1945; Publication (Box 71, Folder 17)
    Author: Robert S. Henry
    Notes: September 1945
  - Item 2: The Unity of the American Railway System, Publication (Box 71, Folder 17)
    Author: W. Jett Lauck
  - Item 3: The Day of Two Noons, Publication (Box 71, Folder 17)
- Box: 71, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Course of Railway Labor Legislation, 1946; Publication (Box 71, Folder 18)
    Author: Daniel P. Loomis
    Notes: July 30, 1946
- Box: 71, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Watson-Parker Law, 1927; Publication (Box 71, Folder 19)
    Author: Wm. Z. Foster
- Box: 71, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Inadequacies of Railway Management, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Inadequacies of Railway Management, Part II, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Inadequacies of Railway Management, Part III, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1962; Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
    Author: Supreme Court of the United States
  - Item 5: The Man in Railroad Management, Publication (Box 71, Folder 20)
    Author: Railway Systems and Management Association
- Box: 71, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Statsbanenes Verkstedforening, Publication (Box 71, Folder 21)
    Author: Sentrum
- Box: 71, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Piggyback: Spearhead of Transportation Progress, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 22)
- Box: 71, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Mechanical Department Safety Rules, 1944; Publication (Box 71, Folder 23)
    Author: The Kansas City Southern Railway Company
    Notes: August 1, 1944
  - Item 2: Our Railways and Their Methods of Subjugation, Publication (Box 71, Folder 23)
    Author: A.L. McKenney
- Box: 71, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Wage Movement, 1920; Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Author: National Publishing Company
  - Item 2: Railroad Retirement Board, Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Author: U.S. Railroad Retirement Board
  - Item 3: Twenty-Five Years of Railroad Social Insurance, Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Progress of Disability Program, Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: Railroads and Railroad Wages, 1938; Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Author: Bureau of Information of the Eastern Railways
  - Item 6: Refunds to Railroad Employees, 1946; Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Notes: June 21, 1946
  - Item 7: Railroad Retirement Act and Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act Amendments, 1968; Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Notes: January 24, 1968
  - Item 8: Average Daily and Monthly Wage Rates of Railroad Employees on Class I Carriers, 1920; Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Author: U.S. Railroad Labor Board
    Notes: August 1920
  - Item 9: Problem Areas in Implementing Amendatory Legislation Affecting Railroad Retirement Annuities, 1968; Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Notes: November 29, 1968
  - Item 10: Amending the Railroad Retirement Act of 1937, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Notes: October 13, 1966
  - Item 11: Railroad Retirement Supplemental Annuities, 1969; Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Notes: July 10, 1969
  - Item 12: Railroad Retirement Benefits, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Item 13: Interim Report of the U.S. Commission on Railroad Retirement, 1971; Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Notes: July 1971
  - Item 14: Railroad Retirement, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Notes: April 29, 1965
  - Item 15: Amending the Railroad Retirement Act of 1937, 1968; Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Notes: January 16, 1968
  - Item 16: Amend Railway Retirement Legislation, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Notes: May 18, 1966
  - Item 17: Railroad Retirement Amendments of 1970, Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Notes: April 16, 1970
  - Item 18: Amending the Railroad Retirement Act of 1937, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 24)
    Notes: June 29, 1965
- Box: 71, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Statistics of Railroads of Class I, 1967; Publication (Box 71, Folder 25)
    Notes: August 1967
  - Item 2: Yearbook of Railroad Facts, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 25)
- Box: 71, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Railroads in Crisis, Publication (Box 71, Folder 26)
    Author: Labor Research Association
- Box: 71, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Stabilization of Employment on the Railroads, 1927; Publication (Box 71, Folder 27)
    Author: Committee on Stabilization of Employment
    Notes: May 26-27, 1927
- Box: 71, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The Meaning of Nationalization, 1965; Publication (Box 71, Folder 28)
    Notes: January 1965
- Box: 71, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Field Independence as a Conceptual Framework for the Prediction of Social and Task-Related Evaluations, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
    Author: Leopold Gruenfeld & Jack Arbuthnot
  - Item 2: Appraisal, Performance and Rating, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
    Author: Robert S. Minor
  - Item 3: Developing and Using Performance Standards, 1937; Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
    Author: Constance M. Ewy
  - Item 4: How to Use Performance Rating, 1952; Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
    Author: Society for Advancement of Management
  - Item 5: Supervisory Characteristics and Attitudes Toward Performance Appraisals, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
    Author: Leopold W. Gruenfeld & Peter Weissenberg
  - Item 6: A Guide for Supervisors, 1949; Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
    Author: Department of the Army
  - Item 7: Employee Performance Appraisal Programs, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
    Author: American Hospital Association
  - Item 8: Man-to-Man Evaluation, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
    Author: T.D. Parenti
  - Item 9: Associate Evaluations: Nominations vs. Ratings, 1974; Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
    Author: Ronald G. Downey
    Notes: September 1974
  - Item 10: Guidelines for Annual Evaluation, Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
    Author: Jack H. Grossman & Julian Frank
  - Item 11: Manual of Performance Standards and Evaluation, 1968; Publication (Box 71, Folder 29)
    Author: Pennsylvania Civil Service Commission
- Box: 71, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Real Estate, Insurance, and Financial Establishments, 1972; Publication (Box 71, Folder 30)
- Box: 71, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Postwar Re-Employment, Publication (Box 71, Folder 31)
    Author: Karl T. Schlotterbeck
  - Item 2: Post-War Problems, 1946; Publication (Box 71, Folder 31)
    Author: Agnes E. Meyer
    Notes: April 22 - May 26, 1946
- Box: 71, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 71, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Recreation Leadership, 1952; Publication (Box 71, Folder 32)
    Author: Walter L. Stone & Charles G. Stone
  - Item 2: Industrial Recreation Facilities, 1945; Publication (Box 71, Folder 32)
    Author: Earl L. Ferris & Floyd R. Eastwood
  - Item 3: Recreation in Industry, 1949; Publication (Box 71, Folder 32)
    Author: Industrial Welfare Society
- Box: 71, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 71, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Recruiting Young Men for Industry, 1948; Publication (Box 71, Folder 34)
    Notes: May 1948
  - Item 2: Le Recrutement et la Selection Dans L'Enterprise, Publication (Box 71, Folder 34)
    Author: Federation des Industries Belges
- Box: 71, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 71, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Operation Native Son, Publication (Box 71, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: College Recruiting in the Internal Revenue Service, Publication (Box 71, Folder 35)
    Author: U.S. Internal Revenue Service
- Box: 71, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 71, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: A Discussion of Major Issues Arising in the Recruitment of Industrial Labor in Peru, 1966; Publication (Box 71, Folder 36)
    Author: David Chaplin
- Box: 71, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 71, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Reed & Prince Manufacturing Co. Labor Dispute, 1952; Publication (Box 71, Folder 37)
- Box: 71, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 71, Folder 38)